// AUTOGENERATED FILE
// DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE UNDER ANY CIRCUMSTANCES
// ALL EDITS MUST BE DONE IN THEIR RESPECTIVE EXCEL SHEETS AND EXPORTED!
// encoding = unicode (16-bit)
x4tagRegionName01=Summer Palace
x4tagRegionName02=Crimson Shore
x4tagRegionName03=Hinterland Marshes
x4tagRegionName04=Haunted Grove
x4tagRegionName05=Abandoned Village
x4tagRegionName06=Riverside
x4tagRegionName07=Upper Wilds
x4tagRegionName08=Haunted Shipwreck
x4tagRegionName09=Flooded Caves
x4tagRegionName10=Lai Farmlands 
x4tagRegionName11=Village of Lai
x4tagRegionName12=Lai Countryside
x4tagRegionName13=Forgotten Tower
x4tagRegionName14=Silk Road Approach
x4tagRegionName15=Silk Road Trading Post
x4tagRegionName16=The Great Wall
x4tagRegionName17=Lakeside Fields
x4tagRegionName18=Ruined Fort
x4tagRegionName19=Hinterlands
x4tagRegionName20=The Crater
x4tagRegionName21=Infested Plains
x4tagRegionName22=Shrine of the Stars
x4tagRegionName23=Imperial Overlook
x4tagRegionName24=Xiao Farmlands
x4tagRegionName25=Fiery Fissure
x4tagRegionName26=Village of Xiao
x4tagRegionName27=Broken Bridge
x4tagRegionName28=Kunlun Approach
x4tagRegionName29=Ruined Fields
x4tagRegionName30=Old Mountain Sanctum
x4tagRegionName31=Valley of the Failed
x4tagRegionName32=Glacial Approach
x4tagRegionName33=Kunlun Monastery
x4tagRegionName34=Slaver Camp
x4tagRegionName35=Emperor's Road
x4tagRegionName36=Pingyang Outskirts
x4tagRegionName37=Trade Quarter
x4tagRegionName38=Palace Gardens
x4tagRegionName39=Palace Exterior
x4tagRegionName40=Mausoleum
x4tagRegionName41=Pingyang Highlands
x4tagRegionName42=Lower Ascent
x4tagRegionName43=Upper Ascent
x4tagRegionName44=The Eight Pillars
x4tagRegionName45=Heavenly Gardens
x4tagRegionName46=Jade Court
x4tagRegionName47=Crystalline Corridors
x4tagRegionName48=Frigid Pools
x4tagRegionName49=Antechamber
x4tagRegionName50=Halls of Sihai Longwang
x4tagRegionName51=Chamber Of The Four Seas
x4tagRegionName52=Asyut Encampment
x4tagRegionName53=Temple Region
x4tagRegionName54=Prosoro's Path
x4tagRegionName55=Necropolis Outskirts
x4tagRegionName56=Abydos Necropolis
x4tagRegionName57=Abydos Barrens
x4tagRegionName58=Nile Valley
x4tagRegionName59=Thebes
x4tagRegionName60=Forsaken Wastes
x4tagRegionName61=Dragon Cavern
x4tagRegionName62= 
x4tagRegionName69=Elemental Cave: Wood
x4tagRegionName70=Evil Sage Cave
x4tagRegionName71=Elemental Cave: Metal
x4tagRegionName72=Roadside Tomb
x4tagRegionName73=Feral Cave
x4tagRegionName74=Tomb of Xu Chu
x4tagRegionName75=Elemental Cave: Water
x4tagRegionName76=Winter Stores
x4tagRegionName77=Elemental Cave: Fire
x4tagRegionName78=Monastery Interior
x4tagRegionName79=Shelter of the Failed
x4tagRegionName80=Elemental Cave: Earth
x4tagRegionName81=Slave Pit
x4tagRegionName82=Imperial Palace
x4tagRegionName83=Underground Tunnels
x4tagRegionName84=Yushi Jade Mine
x4tagRegionName85=Subterranean Kilns
x4tagRegionName86=Golden Idol Cave
x4tagRegionName87=Elemental Cave: Convergence
x4tagRegionName88=Shen's Sanctum
x4tagRegionName89=Collapsed Catacombs
x4tagRegionName90=Flooded Temple of Sobek
x4tagRegionName91=Solar Temple of Ra
x4tagRegionName92=Darktread Caves
x4tagRegionName93=Cavern of Serket
x4tagRegionName94=Funerary Temple Ruins
x4tagRegionName95=Burial Vaults
x4tagRegionName96=Great Osiris Temple
x4tagRegionName97=Osireion Crypts
x4tagRegionName98=Abydos Crypts
x4tagRegionName99=Funerary Chapel
x4tagRegionName99b=Mortuary Back Entrance
x4tagRegionName100=Preparation Chambers
x4tagRegionName101=Mortuary Catacombs
x4tagRegionName102=Thieves' Den
x4tagRegionName103=Temple of Serket
x4tagRegionName104=Cavern of Serket
x4tagRegionName105=Lair of the Forbidden Glyph
x4tagRegionName106=Inner Sanctum
x4tagRegionName107=Crowned Scarab Inn
x4tagRegionName108=Dusty Cellar
x4tagRegionName109=Temple of Hathor
x4tagRegionName110=Palace of Thebes
x4tagRegionName111=Forgotten Tombs
x4tagRegionName112=Temple of Aten
x4tagRegionName113=Riverbed Path 
x4tagRegionName114=Back Road
x4tagRegionName115=Abandoned Farms
x4tagRegionName116=Riverside Pathway
x4tagRegionName117=Infested Bog
x4tagRegionName118=Yaoguai Encampment
x4tagRegionName119=Zhaoze Village
x4tagRegionName120=Path of Fenghuang
x4tagRegionName121=Shi Ya City Approach
x4tagRegionName122=Ravaged Shi Ya Square
x4tagRegionName123=Tiantan
x4tagRegionName124=Breeding Grounds
x4tagRegionName125=Mortuary Temple Ruins
x4tagRegionName126=Thebes Farmlands
x4tagRegionName127=Thebes Borderlands
x4tagRegionName128=Floodplains
x4tagRegionName129=City Outskirts
x4tagRegionName130=Cursed Plateau
x4tagRegionName131=Temple of Aten
x4tagRegionName132=Tower Ruins
x4tagRegionName133=Damp Cave
x4tagRegionName134=Secluded Cave
x4tagRegionName135=Akhenaten's Treasure Chambers
x4tagRegionName136=Flooded Hall
x4tagPrefix01=Daji's
x4tagPrefix02=Clairvoyant's
x4tagPrefix03=Soothsayer's
x4tagSuffix01=of Tranquility
x4tagSuffix02=of Harmony
x4tagSuffix03=of Jin Chan
x4tagSuffix04=of Martial Supremacy
x4tagSuffix05=of the Emperor
x4tagSuffix06=of Celestial Might
x4tagSuffix07=of Aten
x4tagSuffix08=of Seth
x4tagSuffix09=of Serket
x4tagSkillNeidanPotionBuff=Potent Elixir
x4tagSkillNeidanPotionBuffDesc=Neidan practitioners often alter their concoctions to grant them additional boons when imbibed.{^n}{^Y} Can trigger when a health or energy potion is used.
x4tagSkillNeidanConvergence=Convergence
x4tagSkillNeidanConvergenceDesc=The Neidan's body is attuned to the potions themselves, sometimes granting additional unexpected power.{^Y} Can trigger when a health or energy potion is used.
x4tagSkillNeidanEnergyDrain=Chi Realignment
x4tagSkillNeidanEnergyDrainDesc=Realigns an enemy's Chi, wounding them and bolstering your own energies
x4tagSkillNeidanEnergyDrainDisruption=Reverberation
x4tagSkillNeidanEnergyDrainDisruptionDesc=Severe changes to an enemy's Chi leaves them with lasting consequences.
x4tagSkillNeidanShenPao=Shen Pao
x4tagSkillNeidanShenPaoDesc=Throw a volatile alchemical concoction at a foe that detonates on impact and causes random elemental damage.
x4tagSkillNeidanDeathBomb=Echoes of the Ancestors
x4tagSkillNeidanDeathBombDesc=Upon vanquishing enemies with Shen Pao, blast waves emanate from you and deal damage around you.{^n}{^Y} Can trigger on enemy death. 
x4tagSkillNeidanDash=Dash
x4tagSkillNeidanDashDesc=Unleash a burst of chi to move at incredible speed for a short time.
x4tagSkillNeidanDashPhase=Smoke Cloud
x4tagSkillNeidanDashPhaseDesc=You throw a small amount of fine powder which releases a burst of energy blinding and hindering your foes.
x4tagSkillNeidanWeakestChakra=Weakest Chakra
x4tagSkillNeidanWeakestChakraDesc=You become attuned to the elements, emanating lethal energy that diminishes enemy health and weakens their defences. 
x4tagSkillNeidanDragonsBreath=Breath Attack
x4tagSkillNeidanDragonsBreathDesc=You emanate a focused energy attack in a cone in front of you, disorienting your foes.{^n}{^Y}Assign this skill to your left mouse button. 
x4tagSkillNeidanDragonsBreathFearAndFumble=Voice of the Ancients
x4tagSkillNeidanDragonsBreathFearAndFumbleDesc=Enemies caught in your Breath Attack will suffer the wrath of the Elements. 
x4tagSkillNeidanLuckyFind=Blessing of Jin Chan
x4tagSkillNeidanLuckyFindDesc=The blessings of Jin Chan are upon you, granting a chance for additional boons for every enemy slain.{^n}{^Y} Can trigger on enemy death.  
x4tagSkillNeidanGoodFortune=Good Fortune
x4tagSkillNeidanGoodFortuneDesc=Increasing one's wealth may grant other benefits. 
x4tagSkillNeidanAuraOfTranquility=Aura of Tranquility
x4tagSkillNeidanAuraOfTranquilityDesc=Your mind is a weapon and a shield. You use your Chi to create a renewable barrier around you.
x4tagSkillNeidanEbbandFlow=Essence of Jade
x4tagSkillNeidanEbbandFlowDesc=A powerful and mystic mineral, you use jade to sharpen your attack skills even further.
x4tagSkillNeidanMeldingArmor=Melding Armor
x4tagSkillNeidanMeldingArmorDesc=The strength of your Chi’s flow is such that your barrier is imbued with additional protective energies.
x4tagSkillNeidanTerracottaServant=Terracotta Servants
x4tagSkillNeidanTerracottaServantDesc=Throw a masterful alchemical concoction that creates a terracotta warrior at the point of impact that serves you.{^n}{^Y} You can summon more than one terracotta servant at the time. 
x4tagSkillNeidanTerracottaServantShatter=Shatter
x4tagSkillNeidanTerracottaServantShatterDesc=Not even death breaks the bonds of servitude. Upon expiring or being killed your terracotta servant shatters, dealing damage around him. 
x4tagSkillNeidanTerracottaServantTeachingsOfTheMaster=Forged by Fire
x4tagSkillNeidanTerracottaServantTeachingsOfTheMasterDesc=Creates an aura around the terracotta servant damaging him and enemies around him. 
x4tagSkillNeidanConsequences=Consequences
x4tagSkillNeidanConsequencesDesc=You channel power through your weapon lowering your enemies' resistance to damage.{^n}{^Y} Weapon attacks have a chance to reduce enemies’ resistances. 
x4tagSkillNeidanLastingConsequences=Huangdi's Favor
x4tagSkillNeidanLastingConsequencesDesc=You channel the wrath of Emperors past and strike your foes with lightning. 
x4tagSkillNeidanSplash=Spreading Influence
x4tagSkillNeidanSplashDesc=Upon hitting an enemy, your attacks deal damage in an area, damaging enemies around it.
x4tagSkillNeidanSpreadingRot=Mutual Suffering
x4tagSkillNeidanSpreadingRotDesc=Stricken enemies may spread death and feebleness around them upon death.{^n}{^Y} Slain enemies can spread Consequences debuff on death.
x4tagNeidanMastery=Neidan Mastery
x4tagNeidanMasteryDescription=Master Neidan, the art of internal and external alchemy. Using a combination of deadly concoctions and abilities that make use of their inner energies, Neidan masters are a force to be reckoned with.
x4tagNeidan=Neidan
x4tagNeidanStorm=Channeler
x4tagNeidanDefense=Monk
x4tagNeidanEarth=Wu
x4tagNeidanNature=Hermit
x4tagNeidanWarfare=Daoist
x4tagNeidanHunting=Pilgrim
x4tagNeidanSpirit=Spiritualist
x4tagNeidanRogue=Disruptor
x4tagNeidanDream=Contemplator
x4tagNeidanRune=Esoterist
x4tagMChina=The East
x4tagMZone01=Summer Palace
x4tagMZone02=Xiao
x4tagMZone03=Pingyang
x4tagMZone04=The Ascent 
x4tagMZone05=Heavenly Palace
x4tagMZone06=Asyut Encampment
x4tagMZone07=Necropolis Outskirts
x4tagMZone08=Thebes
x4tagMZone09=Scorched Ridge
x4tagMZone10=Lai
x4tagMPortal01=Summer Palace Portal
x4tagMPortal02=Xiao Portal
x4tagMPortal03=Pingyang Portal
x4tagMPortal04=The Ascent Portal
x4tagMPortal05=Heavenly Palace Portal
x4tagMPortal06=Asyut Encampment Portal
x4tagMPortal07=Necropolis Outskirts Portal
x4tagMPortal08=Thebes Portal
x4tagMPortal09=Scorched Ridge Portal
x4tagMPortal10=Lai Portal
x4tag_PotionOfSpeed=Potion of Speed
x4tag_PotionOfAmbrosia=Potion of Ambrosia
x4tag_PotionOfService=Potion of Service
x4tag_PotionWuTaosElixir=Wu Tao's Elixir
x4tag_PotionJadeEmperorsResolve=Potion of the Jade Emperor's Resolve
x4tag_PotionOfEvasion=Potion of Evasion
x4tag_PotionLifeDrainer=Potion of Life Draining
x4tag_PotionOfNewBeginnings=Potion of New Beginnings
x4tag_PotionOfSpeedDesc=This potion increases your base movement speed.
x4tag_PotionOfAmbrosiaDesc=This potion increases your primary resistances.
x4tag_PotionOfServiceDesc=This potion increases your base armor.
x4tag_PotionWuTaosElixirDesc=This potion increases your bleeding and poison resistance.
x4tag_PotionJadeEmperorsResolveDesc=This potion increases your secondary resistances.
x4tag_PotionOfEvasionDesc=This potion increases your dodge and projectile avoidance chance.
x4tag_PotionLifeDrainerDesc=This potion converts a portion of the damage you deal to Life Leech.
x4tag_PotionOfNewBeginningsDesc=This potion resets your spent attribute points.
x4tagSkill_Artifact_Abdicate=Abdicate
x4tagSkill_Artifact_DeathsToll=Death's Toll
x4tagSkill_Artifact_Discharge=Discharge
x4tagSkill_Artifact_Endure=Endure
x4tagSkill_Artifact_AbdicateDesc=Strike terror into your enemies' hearts, temporarily reducing their maximum health, slowing them, and increasing their vulnerability.
x4tagSkill_Artifact_DeathsTollDesc=Succumb to a state of frenzy, gaining speed, damage, and resistances with every kill.
x4tagSkill_Artifact_DischargeDesc=Imbue your weapons with the wrath of a tempest, temporarily dealing electrical and cold damage with every strike and exposing your enemies' weaknesses.
x4tagSkill_Artifact_EndureDesc=Flood your body with magic, increasing resilience while wielding axes.
Note_NeidanLetter=Yin Lihua, {^n}{^n}I understand you wish to end your apprenticeship, and I accept your decision. Perhaps it is better this way – you had many virtues, but patience was not one of them.{^n}Six years ago, you sought my mentorship to master Neidan, the art of internal alchemy. I had concerns: You were hot-tempered and quick to judge. And even though you never said so, I know it was not only health and wisdom you seek, but also immortality and power to find revenge against those who took your daughter’s life. Despite all this, I accepted. Why, you ask? Because I can tell a just soul when I see it. Because in your eyes lurked a pain which I know all too well. {^n}{^n}Six years, I trained you, helped you cultivate your Jing, soothe your Qi, and help see your Shen. I taught you my most secret concoctions and recipes, even those meant to harm and not heal. Six years, I felt nothing but pride when I saw you train in the courtyard, up before dawn like every day, driven by that force of will that writes history. {^n}And while it may be true that you have learned all I could teach you, I cannot but wonder: what kind of apprentice makes such a decision without at least looking her master in the eye? Where was this courage you always spoke of?You are a warrior of Neidan now, Yin Lihua, and may it serve you well on the bloody path before you. But if there is one last bit of advice you may take from your old master, let it be this: some demons lurk on the inside. And they cannot be slain like the rest. {^n}{^n}I wish you longevity,{^n}Your Master Fa Xian
Note_HuizhongLetter=My dear friend Ma Yuan,{^n}{^n}I thank you for your kind words. You advise me not to worry, to trust in our Lord, the Son of Heaven’s, wisdom and guidance. And I try, Ma Yuan, I truly try. But tell me this, my dear friend: how much trust does a leader need to reassure a fearful farmer whose fields the Suns’ rage has turned barren? How much trust to inspire the village guards, green-faced boys and pitchfork-wielding men, to stand against the many beasts the Great Peril’s appearance has brought back into our lands? How much trust to console a mother who lost her boy to their claws?{^n}I am no blasphemer. I believe in the Son of Heaven’s wisdom, for he is divine. But I also believe that only trust and faith have yet to vanquish a threat such as the one we face. {^n}Ancestors know we cannot best it alone.{^n}{^n}Sincerely,{^n}Your Friend Huizhong
Note_MogwaiBit=Numerous as the Mogwai are, scholars are still in disagreement as to their origins. While old theories suggest they are nothing but malicious demon spawn with a penchant for malice and destruction, some scholars now offer an alternative explanation: that the Mogwai are actually vengeful spirits seeking to destroy those that caused their suffering. Said scholars also suggest that a monetary sacrifice—coins placed in a bowl at the doorstep—may appease the Mogwai by giving them the funds to traverse the afterlife, but this theory remains shadily doubtful. Whatever the truth, one thing remains certain: if a Mogwai crosses your path, running or fighting is doubtlessly the best course of action.
Note_QiongQiReport=Lieutenant,{^n}{^n}I understand your frustration and apologize deeply. However, it was simply not possible – or beyond my capabilities – to extract any useful information from the poor man, as the events have turned him fully catatonic. Besides describing Qiong Qi’s gruesome attack, all I could get out of him was a confused ramble about fire and the suns. I imagine he refers to the horrible drought. {^n}Let us hope future witnesses bring more clarity.{^n}{^n}Heavens guide you,{^n}Lu Buwei
Note_BookOfTheDeadNote=My Lord, {^n}{^n}I have investigated the matter as per your request. Your suspicions were correct—some does indeed seem to have stolen the Book of the Dead. I shall investigate the matter further.{^n}{^n}Your humble servant,{^n}Yanluo Wang
Note_ReliefedPriest=In peace, Amenmose,{^n}{^n}They say to never speak ill of the pharaoh, for the gods see and hear it all, yet I am certain they would not mind hearing this: it is finally over. After seventeen years of his madness, Akhenaten and his wife Nefertiti are finally dead. They were poisoned, but I do not know nor care by whom—gods know his enemies were countless. {^n}According to word of mouth, they are already preparing his son’s Tutankhamun’s initiation, and it appears Ay will be the new vizier. No one knows where his loyalties lie or what his goals are, but he does have a reputation for being a pragmatist, so I am certain he will put an end to Akhenaten’s mad sun worship cult and lead people back to the pantheon. {^n}Do you know what this means, Amenmose? No more hiding our faith. No more burning of our statues. Our temples will once again shine in all their splendor, full of supplicants of the true faith. All that remains for us to do is to pray we have not yet fallen from grace.{^n}{^n}In deepest friendship,{^n}Duaenre
Note_YingAndYang=Those who wish to understand the Tao must first understand this: the world is a contrast. {^n}Light and dark. Water and fire. Big and small. Neither of these aspects would have meaning without an opposite quality – the yin to the yang, and the yang to the yin. Because there is night, there is day, because there is good, there is evil; they are inevitable.{^n}But if they are, why do they matter to the Taoist? It is simple: they help us see. If the practitioner encounters a problem, physical or spiritual, personal or global, he calmly sees the dry duality where others see only a projection of their own ambitions, fears and wishes. Only once such lucid vision has been attained, the Taoist can and should proceed to act. 
Note_UndeadReport=Commander Azibo,{^n}{^n}I fear the news are dire; the entire desert seems to be crawling with undead. I have tried to track down their nest, but I could not advance far enough; they are simply too many. I am no arcanist, so I cannot say what has caused them to rise, but even I sense a sickening overpowering unease in the desert; it is as though great powers are at work.{^n}It is not my position to advise you, Commander, yet my duties as a Theban command I do so: you must urge the pharaoh and the vizier to not take this threat lightly. Our walls are high, but there is only so much one can do if the foes you are fighting are already dead.{^n}{^n}In peace,{^n}Scout Zuka
Note_BaoNotes=Sun too hot. Bao not like, make skin yuck and shiny things melt. Bao want smash suns, but suns up too high. Maybe human help?
Note_Pamphlet=The line of Pharaoh’s has become corrupt! Their blasphemy and debauchery has gone to far. Oh, great people of Egypt, save your souls, worship the gods with all your heart, and trust your priests to deliver you from sin. Trust your priests to guide you for they are the only ones who know the path to salvation. Let them rule you in matters of body and soul. {^n}{^n}May the blessings of Ra be upon you, you who have suffered so much.   
Note_Qilin=Qilin. The benevolent chimera. {^n}{^n}As it is the case with many divine and supernatural creatures, legends shroud the qilin like stardust; and since sightings of these beautiful beings are so rare and reports differ, it might always remain this way. What almost all of them agree on is this: with beards, upwards-flowing manes, and antlers, qilin resemble wingless dragons. Some witnesses said parts of them were aflame when they appeared, though the fire did them no harm; others say soft down feathers adorn their scales like a most magnificent bird, while another source claims to have seen fishlike scales and bedazzling jewelry.{^n}{^n}Another certainty is this: while a qilin’s magic is powerful, they never harm innocents, seeking exclusively to punish the wicked. Furthermore, their appearance can be seen as an omen of good. Thus, it came as no surprise, when, during the Son of Heaven’s coronation, an entire herd of them appeared at the palace courtyard.
Note_Guardsman=Dear Ziying,{^n}{^n}A drought ravages the land and Qiong Qi of the Great Perils and his minions are butchering innocents by the dozens, yet all this lowlife brigand scum can think about is looting and plundering, like carrion crows feeding off the corpses. So how could I not be upset? Mankind is so quick to complain about its many travails, yet, since we evolved from Pangu’s mites, all we do is tear at each other’s throats. Ancestors forgive me for saying this, but perhaps it would be better if Qiong Qi made short work of us all.But here I am again, being all pessimistic. I will try to be better, my friend. I will try.{^n}{^n}I wish you longevity,{^n}Zhao
Note_HunAndPo=Understand, pupil of the Tao: death is not the end.{^n}It is common knowledge that we continue to exist after death: like everything in this world, we are made of a yin and a yang, the po and the hun.  When we perish, the po splits into two fragments, one of which stays in our buried body, while the other ascends to the Heavens to be judged; the hun, however, remains in the spirit tablet by our grave. {^n}While you may assume our hun and po are immortal, for we have already died, they are wrong: both must be nourished and tended to by our descendants, until, with time, the hun ascends to heaven, only to later descend to the underworld together with the po.{^n}Why is it important to follow the rituals and tend to the deceased’s hun and po? Simple: if you do not, their ghost may come to haunt you.{^n}But this is a story for another scroll.
Note_Unhaunting_Manual_01=If you are reading this, odds are you are experiencing a rather unpleasant event: you are being haunted by a ghost or guei. But do not despair, my friend, for every haunting can be ended, and The Ghost Expert’s Manual to Unhaunting will show you how.{^n}{^n}The first step must always be to identify the nature of the haunting, hun or po. Let us start with the latter: as you well know, the po is the part of us that stays in our bodies when we perish; when a po haunting occurs, the ghost will return in its original, often decomposing form, which can be a rather unpleasant sight.{^n}The hun haunting, on the other hand, can be infinitely more pernicious; as the hun is the part of us that contains our personality, during a hun haunting, the haunted often sees the ghost in their dreams, or some other incorporeal form.{^n}Now, doubtlessly, the following question burns on your mind: what to do? How do you “un-haunt” yourself?{^n}{^n}I fear to the answer, you will have to buy, The Ghost Expert’s Manual to Unhaunting, Volume 2!
Note_Unhaunting_Manual_02=If you are reading this, it means you have already basked in the semantic beauty of The Ghost Expert’s Manual to Unhaunting, Volume 1. If not, I strongly recommend you buy it first, for many of the stunning insights provided in Volume 2 may be hard to comprehend otherwise.{^n}{^n}As discussed in the previous volume, there are two types of hauntings, po and hun, corporeal and ethereal. First, here is the good news: most hauntings of either type can be easily remedied by doing what, if I may say so, you should have done before.{^n}Follow the burial customs.{^n}You heard right, my friend: the majority of hauntings is caused by improper burial customs. Kindly assuming you are not a heathen or simply disrespectful, I will omit a lengthy compilation of what these customs are – as you know, there are many. Even so, believe me when I say, that a simple candle or properly placed burial mound has solved many a client’s tribulations.{^n}{^n}If you followed the burial customs or the guei is not even related to you, things might be more difficult. Quite unfortunately, however, my ink has just run out, so I will explain what’s needed in the next volume, The Ghost Expert’s Manual to Unhaunting, Volume 3!
Note_Unhaunting_Manual_03=Friend! Client! Haunting-afflicted Soul! It is my pleasure to welcome you to the The Ghost Expert’s Manual to Unhaunting, Volume 3, the sadly last volume of this immensely helpful and affordable guide to unhaunting.{^n}{^n}If you are still reading, it means that your haunting cannot be traced back to improper burial customs. Unfortunate.{^n}{^n}My friend, let me ask you this: have you ever acted unvirtuously? And no, I am not talking of the sweets you stole as a child or the canoodling you engaged in before marriage. I am talking about broken oaths, dubious bargains, betrayed lovers, and things far more sinister to mention. Often, the ghosts who return despite being properly buried do so because they have been wronged, and most likely by the target of their haunting. {^n}{^n}What do I do, you ask me? Simple: undo the wrong. Make amends. Depending on the scope of your misdemeanor, this may bring the restless soul to rest. And if not? Then, my dear friend, you are well and thoroughly done for. {^n}Good luck!
Note_To_Whom_It_May_Concern=That’s it. I’ve had it! Day in and day out we raid the human villages…why do they have to make it so difficult? Pitchfork this, cudgel that. And now there’s rumor of an insane Greek travelling the land, killing everything in sight. No thank you, my insurance doesn’t cover foreign invasions. Apparently two mages in the West are hiring extras for their show – they even provide dental. The audition is tomorrow, wish me luck!{^n}{^n}Signed, {^n}Mittens 
Note_Overtime!?=Overtime! Really?! Even when I’m dead?! The nerve of some people! Was I not a good servant in life? Did I not do enough? Build a city he said. Build temples to Aten he said. All that and I still get called back? {^n}{^n}And on top of all that, I can’t even understand him anymore. All he does is rave on about the Sun and flames, burn this, burn that. Now he wants a temple and all I’ve been given is a skeleton crew… he will be the death of me…again (hopefully).
Note_Odin_Help_Me=Odin help me what are these people on about?! I can’t understand any of them. And what are these helmets without horns? Ever since I devoured the soul of that weird blonde man from far away, I have been seeing things differently. I think I will go west, build a ship and find some coasts to raid as is proper.{^n}{^n}Wiedersehen,{^n}Gustav
x4tagMenuCreateX4Char=Legendary Hero
x4tagBoostedCharDesc=You are creating a hero of suitable level and wealth for adventures in the East. The journey begins at the start of the Eternal Embers campaign on Legendary Difficulty. Characters created this way cannot enter Normal or Epic difficulty. 
x4tagRaceHumankind=Humankind
xtag4MoveOnly=Move Only
x4tagTravelQuestion_01=Go through the passage?
x4tagWarriorArmorRack=Warrior's Armor Rack
x4tagHunterArmorRack=Hunter's Armor Rack
x4tagSorcererArmorRack=Sage's Armor Rack
x4tagExperienceGain={%+.0f0}% Experience Gained
x4tag_MQJC002_Reward=+10 Points to Str/Int/Dex
x4tag_SQ_301_Reward=+10% Vitality Damage Resistance
x4tagImperialChest=Imperial Chest
x4tagBoostedCharServerDesc=Unable to connect. You cannot access lower difficulties with this character because it was created with the Legendary Hero boost.
x4tagCanopicJar=Canopic Jar
x4tagPot=Pot
x4tagCoffin=Coffin
x4tagContrast=Contrast
x4tagContrastDescription=Set screen contrast
x4tagBrightness=Brightness
x4tagBrightnessDescription=Set screen brightness
x4tagInviteFriends=Invite Friends
x4tagBackground05=Eternal Embers
x4tagEternalIntro=Eternal Embers Intro
x4tagEternalOutro=Eternal Embers Outro 
tagBuyDLC3=Get Eternal Embers
x4tagStoryScroll_China=Mystic Tome
x4tagStoryScroll_Egypt=Ancient Papyrus Treatise
Note_NeidanLetterTitle=Letter to Yin Lihua
Note_HuizhongLetterTitle=Worries
Note_MogwaiBitTitle=Mogwai 101
Note_QiongQiReportTitle=Field Report
Note_BookOfTheDeadNoteTitle=Theft
Note_ReliefedPriestTitle=An End To The Madness
Note_YingAndYangTitle=The Principles Of Tao
Note_UndeadReportTitle=The Army Of The Dead
Note_BaoNotesTitle=BAO PROPERTY, NO TOUCH
Note_PamphletTitle=Rise! Resist!
Note_QilinTitle=A Study Of The Qilin
Note_GuardsmanTitle=Bandit Scum!
Note_HunAndPoTitle=Hun And Po
Note_Unhaunting_Manual_01Title=Unhaunting Manual: Vol. 1
Note_Unhaunting_Manual_02Title=Unhaunting Manual: Vol. 2
Note_Unhaunting_Manual_03Title=Unhaunting Manual: Vol. 3
Note_To_Whom_It_May_ConcernTitle=To Whom It May Concern
Note_Overtime!?Title=Overtime?!
Note_Odin_Help_MeTitle=Dietary Changes
x4tagAkhenatenPillarDebuff01=Corrupted Shrine: Vitality Drain
x4tagAkhenatenPillarDebuff02=Corrupted Shrine: Poison Touch
x4tagAkhenatenPillarDebuff03=Corrupted Shrine: Torpor
x4tagAkhenatenPillarDebuff04=Corrupted Shrine: Weakness
x4tagAkhenatenPillarDebuffDesc01=While in range, drains life force.
x4tagAkhenatenPillarDebuffDesc02=While in range, deals poison damage.
x4tagAkhenatenPillarDebuffDesc03=While in range, slows movement speed.
x4tagAkhenatenPillarDebuffDesc04=While in range, decreases resistances.
x4tagAkhenatenPillar=Corrupted Shrine
SkillChanceWeightFloat={%.1f0}% Chance to be Used
x4tagSunsNovaDebuff01=Nova
x4tagSunsNovaDebuff01Desc=Damages and slows the player while increasing the power and resistance of enemies if standing in the blasted area.
